Guide to the Vice President for Development and University Relations records, 1820-2003 RG0005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Columbian College Departmental Publicity, 1986-2004; RG0005 Series 9; 0.25 Linear Feet
  - American Studies brochures, newsletters, 1986-2002; RG0005 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Journalism newsletters, student handbook, brochures, press releases, 1991-1997; RG0005 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Judaic Studies newsletters, class listings, 1998-2000; RG0005 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 6)